<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Emmanuel Atoe</title><description>Emmanuel Atoe, Author and Christian Counsellor.</description><link>https://www.eoatoe.com</link><copyright>Copyright (C) 2020 Emmanuel Atoe. All rights reserved.</copyright><item><title>Powerful Daily Confession August 2021</title><description>Galatians 3:13-14 New International Version (NIV)"Christ redeemed us from the curse of the law by becoming a curse for us, for it is written: "Cursed is everyone who is hung on a pole. He redeemed us in order that the blessing given to Abraham might come to the Gentiles through Christ Jesus, so that by faith we might receive the promise of the Spirit." Ephesians 1:17-23 New International Version (NIV)"I keep asking that the God of our Lord Jesus Christ, the glorious Father, may give you the Spirit of wisdom and revelation, so that you may know him better. I pray that the eyes of your heart may be enlightened in order that you may know the hope to which he has called you, the riches of his glorious inheritance in his holy people, and his incomparably great power for us who believe. That power is the same as the mighty strength.  he exerted when he raised Christ from the dead and seated him at his right hand in the heavenly realms, far above al...</description><link>https://www.eoatoe.com/meditation?meditation=powerful-daily-confession-august-2021</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Blessed To Be Blessing</title><description>Ephesians 1:3 (NIV) "Praise be to the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, who has blessed us in the heavenly realms with every spiritual blessing in Christ."How many of you have your bibles with you? Raise it high, kiss it and let's give glory to the almighty Father.  Then make this declaration: You are blessed to be a blessingI am blessed to be a blessing. Thank God, we're blessed to be a blessing.    Genesis 12:1-3 (NIV) "The Lord had said to Abram, "Go from your country, your people and your father's household to the land I will show you. I will make you into a great nation, and I will bless you; I will make your name great, and you will be a blessing.  I will bless those who bless you, and whoever curses you I will curse; and all peoples on earth will be blessed through you."Romans 8:16-17 (NIV) "The Spirit himself testifies with our spirit that we are God's child...</description><link>https://www.eoatoe.com/meditation?meditation=blessed-to-be-blessing</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item><item><title>Prayers for July</title><description>"Listen to my prayer, O God, do not ignore my plea; hear me and answer me. My thoughts trouble me and I am distraught. Evening, morning and noon. I cry out in distress, and he hears my voice." - Psalm 55:1, 2, 17. (NIV) Almighty God, by your power add more people into the church with your character, in the name of Jesus.Every enemy of salvation in the body of Christ, be frustrated, in the name of Jesus.Heavenly father, empower me to be an agent of multiplication in the church, in the name of Jesus. Blood of Jesus, speak against every enemy of church growth, in the name of Jesus.Ancient of days, deliver me from blocking your plan and purpose in the body of Christ, in the name of Jesus.By the anointing that break every yoke, I destroy every property of the devil against church growth, in the name of Jesus.Every organized darkness fighting against church growth, be disorganized, in the name of Jesus.Father Lord, restore your lost love, care, and c...</description><link>https://www.eoatoe.com/prayer?prayer=prayers-for-july</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate></item></channel></rss>